{
    "id": "afb3cca202284abd85a2186d8fbf8c38",
    "title": "Grammar Review Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I met her in Ireland ………………………",
            "description": "We use ago with a past tense and a past time expression to count back from the present.",
            "answers": [
                "six months before",
                "before six months",
                "six months ago"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "24caaab268b744cd9409ee0d3c64591b"
        },
        {
            "question": "The two sisters are very much ………………………",
            "description": "Alike means like each other.",
            "answers": [
                "like",
                "alike",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "488ec11827364d4ebdcda93ca76099bd"
        },
        {
            "question": "Have you been here ……………………..?",
            "description": "Before is used with a perfect tense and no time expression to mean ‘at any time before now/then.’",
            "answers": [
                "ago",
                "before",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6d25484dbcfd45c1b0c39376c6db1221"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………….. the people were singing and dancing.",
            "description": "All or all of can both be used before a noun with a determiner.",
            "answers": [
                "All",
                "All of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f614bd0a7772461ca7d720a387e353b2"
        },
        {
            "question": "I would quite like to go out, …………………….. it is a bit late.",
            "description": "Though and although are interchangeable.",
            "answers": [
                "although",
                "though",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b9a0dfcf497240bb8775b3568ef5269d"
        },
        {
            "question": "‘Lovely day.’ ‘Yes. Bit warm, ………………………..’",
            "description": "Though can be used as an adverb. Although cannot be used as an adverb.",
            "answers": [
                "although",
                "though",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b9fada4a9d48474894a7d6bdb80d2e7f"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is important that she ………………………… told.",
            "description": "In American English, the structure without should is more common.",
            "answers": [
                "be",
                "should be",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "86499a34186149bea46be974d541b363"
        },
        {
            "question": "She looks ……………………… she is going to cry.",
            "description": "Like is possible here in an informal style.",
            "answers": [
                "like",
                "as if",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "60459e64e93749e1bb2378b754d4ee8c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Those candies were wonderful. Could I have …………………………… one?",
            "description": "Another can mean ‘an additional or extra’. It is used after plural nouns.",
            "answers": [
                "other",
                "another",
                "more"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d9054e6d01b847a9a67a3cfa9af9804d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Those peas were delicious. Could I have ………………………..?",
            "description": "With plural and uncountable nouns we normally use more, not other.",
            "answers": [
                "another",
                "other",
                "some more"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "2c2f47a6337647f388f2cf3912ce2949"
        },
        {
            "question": "I didn’t like ………………………. the movies.",
            "description": "We use any of before a noun with a determiner.",
            "answers": [
                "any",
                "any of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a2e8bb8a852e4b398e7ff1e1e38b3f31"
        },
        {
            "question": "Prices keep ………………………",
            "description": "Rise means get higher/go up. Arise means begin or appear. ",
            "answers": [
                "rising",
                "arising",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "897af9e210bd4f1b8fe63da14958e884"
        }
    ]
}